Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box: 36, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Sales Management: A Career For You, 1967; Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Box: 36, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Employee Savings Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Box: 36, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Comprehensive Medical Expense Benefit Plan, 1970; Publication (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Box: 36, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Termination Allowances Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Box: 36, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Facts About., 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Box: 36, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization, 1970; Publication (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Box: 36, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Financial and Operating Statistics, 1969; Publication (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Box: 36, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Chart, 1970; Publication (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Box: 36, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Box: 36, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Box: 36, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Benefit Plans, 1967; Publication (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Box: 36, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Employees Relations Department, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Box: 36, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1967; Publication (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Box: 36, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1972; Publication (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Box: 36, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Chart, 1976; Publication (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Box: 36, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations, 1976; Publication (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Box: 36, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: A Primer On Solid Waste, 1973; Publication (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Box: 36, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: A Primer On Air Pollution, 1971; Publication (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Box: 36, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: A Primer On Water Pollution, 1973; Publication (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Box: 36, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations Chart, 1973; Publication (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Box: 36, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Employee Savings Plan, 1972; Publication (Box 36, Folder 36)
- Box: 36, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Medical Services, 1960; Publication (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Box: 36, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Simplified Safety, 1963; Publication (Box 36, Folder 38)
- Box: 36, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Group Life Insurance Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 36, Folder 39)
- Box: 36, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Pooled Group Life Insurance Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 36, Folder 40)
- Box: 36, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Voluntary Group Life Insurance Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 41)
- Box: 36, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 42)
- Box: 36, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 36, Folder 43)
- Box: 36, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income For Pilots, 1963; Publication (Box 36, Folder 44)
- Box: 36, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Long Term Disability Insurance, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 45)
- Box: 36, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 36, Folder 46)
- Box: 36, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Personnel Development Activities Quarterly Review, 1959; Publication (Box 36, Folder 47)
- Box: 36, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income Plan For Mechanical, Stores and Related Personnel, 1963; Publication (Box 36, Folder 48)
- Box: 36, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income For Pilots, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 49)
- Box: 36, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income Plan For Station, Clerical, Treasury and Supervisory Panel, 1965; Publication (Box 36, Folder 50)
- Box: 36, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 51)
- Box: 36, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Cash Sickness Disability Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 52)
- Box: 36, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: The Travelers Insurance Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 53)
- Box: 36, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Salary Employee Rating Form, 1960; Publication (Box 36, Folder 54)
- Box: 36, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan For Employees, 1948; Publication (Box 36, Folder 55)
- Box: 36, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Safety News, 1959; Publication (Box 36, Folder 56)
- Box: 36, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Accident and Fire Information Bulletin, 1959; Publication (Box 36, Folder 57)
- Box: 36, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Tuition Payment Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 36, Folder 58)
- Box: 36, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Tuition Refund Program, Publication (Box 36, Folder 59)
- Box: 36, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 36, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Personnel Services, Publication (Box 36, Folder 60)
- Box: 36, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Added Values For You, 1973; Publication (Box 36, Folder 61)
- Box: 36, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, Publication (Box 36, Folder 62)
- Box: 36, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 36, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Retirement For Hourly Employees, 1959; Publication (Box 36, Folder 63)
- Box: 36, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 36, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Insurance For You and Yours, 1959; Publication (Box 36, Folder 64)
- Box: 36, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 36, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Here's Insurance For You and Yours (Hourly Employees), 1959; Publication (Box 36, Folder 65)
- Box: 36, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 36, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan For Salaried Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 36, Folder 66)
- Box: 36, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 36, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Added Values For You, 1973; Publication (Box 36, Folder 67)
- Box: 36, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 36, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Insurance For You and Yours (Retired Employees), 1959; Publication (Box 36, Folder 68)
- Box: 36, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 36, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Introduction of New Employees, Publication (Box 36, Folder 69)
- Box: 36, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 36, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Retirement Counseling Program, 1953; Publication (Box 36, Folder 70)
- Box: 36, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 36, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Employees Stock Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 71)
- Box: 36, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 36, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Bonus Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 36, Folder 72)
- Box: 36, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 36, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: 1956 Employees' Stock Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 73)
- Box: 36, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 36, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Hospital Expense and Surgical Operation Insurance After Retirement, 1957; Publication (Box 36, Folder 74)
- Box: 36, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 36, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Expense Benefits, 1956; Publication (Box 36, Folder 75)
- Box: 36, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 36, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: As You Enter The Armed Forces, 1953; Publication (Box 36, Folder 76)
- Box: 36, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 36, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Handbook, Publication (Box 36, Folder 77)
- Box: 36, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 36, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Holders of The Personnel Administration Manual, 1970; Publication (Box 36, Folder 78)
- Box: 36, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 36, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Training Practical Politics, 1964; Publication (Box 36, Folder 79)
- Box: 36, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 36, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1967; Publication (Box 36, Folder 80)
- Box: 36, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 36, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Des Sciences Sociales, Economiques Et Politiques, 1958; Publication (Box 36, Folder 81)
- Box: 36, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 36, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Educational Aid Program, 1964; Publication (Box 36, Folder 82)
    Author: J. Bebbington
- Box: 36, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 36, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Notice, 1964; Publication (Box 36, Folder 83)
    Author: Forrest E. Votow
- Box: 36, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 36, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Letter To Presidents and General Manager, 1962; Publication (Box 36, Folder 84)
    Author: R.S. Ingersoll
- Box: 36, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 36, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Wrapping Up Tomorrow For You, Publication (Box 36, Folder 85)
- Box: 36, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 36, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: The Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 86)
- Box: 36, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 36, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Safety Guide, Publication (Box 36, Folder 87)
- Box: 36, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 36, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 36, Folder 88)
- Box: 36, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 36, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Civil Defense Program, 1962; Publication (Box 36, Folder 89)
- Box: 36, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 36, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Your Mony Investment Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 36, Folder 90)
- Box: 36, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 36, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Security Plan For Employees, 1961; Publication (Box 36, Folder 91)
- Box: 36, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 36, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Benefits For Employees, 1968; Publication (Box 36, Folder 92)
- Box: 36, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 36, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Benefits For Employees, 1962; Publication (Box 36, Folder 93)
- Box: 36, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 36, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Principles of Supervision, Publication (Box 36, Folder 94)
- Box: 36, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 36, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Elements of Leadership, Publication (Box 36, Folder 95)
- Box: 36, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 36, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Senior Serviceman Training Course, 1954; Publication (Box 36, Folder 96)
- Box: 36, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 36, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Product Catalog, 1962; Publication (Box 36, Folder 97)
- Box: 36, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 36, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Your Future Years, 1963; Publication (Box 36, Folder 98)
- Box: 36, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 36, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Your Group Insurance Program, 1950; Publication (Box 36, Folder 99)
- Box: 36, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 36, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan For Salaried Employees, 1962; Publication (Box 36, Folder 100)
- Box: 36, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 36, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Tuition Refund Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 101)
- Box: 36, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 36, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Conference Leadership: A Manual, 1958; Publication (Box 36, Folder 102)
- Box: 36, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 36, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Employees' Merit Rating Report, Publication (Box 36, Folder 103)
- Box: 36, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 36, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Supplementary Retirement Program, Publication (Box 36, Folder 104)
- Box: 36, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 36, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: Retirement Association, Publication (Box 36, Folder 105)
- Box: 36, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 36, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Outline of Insurance and Retirement Plans For Members of The Faculty, 1951; Publication (Box 36, Folder 106)
- Box: 36, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 36, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: Objectives and Goals, 1962; Publication (Box 36, Folder 107)
- Box: 36, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 36, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: Effective Communications In Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 36, Folder 108)
- Box: 36, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 36, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: The Labor Education Program, Publication (Box 36, Folder 109)
- Box: 36, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 36, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: The Labor Education Program, 1962; Publication (Box 36, Folder 110)
- Box: 36, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 36, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: Twelfth Annual Industrial Relations, 1954; Publication (Box 36, Folder 111)
- Box: 36, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 36, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: Center For Continuation Study and Industrial Relations Center, 1961; Publication (Box 36, Folder 112)
- Box: 36, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 36, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: Program of the Industrial Relations Center, 1950; Publication (Box 36, Folder 113)
- Box: 36, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 36, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Center Chart Book, 1948; Publication (Box 36, Folder 114)
- Box: 36, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 36, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: Group Health Care Program, 1968; Publication (Box 36, Folder 115)
- Box: 36, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 36, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: Safety In Mobil Chemical, 1967; Publication (Box 36, Folder 116)
    Author: C.S. Dedon
- Box: 36, Folder: 117, Publication (Box 36, Folder 117)
  - Item 1: A Report To The Financial Community, 1966; Publication (Box 36, Folder 117)
- Box: 36, Folder: 118, Publication (Box 36, Folder 118)
  - Item 1: Comprehensive Medical Expense Benefit Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 36, Folder 118)
- Box: 36, Folder: 119, Publication (Box 36, Folder 119)
  - Item 1: Safety In Petroleum Marketing, 1958; Publication (Box 36, Folder 119)
- Box: 36, Folder: 120, Publication (Box 36, Folder 120)
  - Item 1: Safety In Research and Engineering, 1967; Publication (Box 36, Folder 120)
- Box: 37, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Foreman Training Cause, 1961; Publication (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Box: 37, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Training, 1949; Publication (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Box: 37, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Monograph, 1957; Publication (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Box: 37, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Audit, 1948; Publication (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Box: 37, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Monograph On Job Rating, 1961; Publication (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Box: 37, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Job Rating Manual, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Box: 37, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Your Hourly Rate and How It Is Determined, Publication (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Box: 37, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Job Rating Manual, 1957; Publication (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Box: 37, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: How To Put Your Ideas Across To Restaurant Workers, 1955; Publication (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Box: 37, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Personnel Policies and Practice Pay Off With The Restaurant Customer, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Box: 37, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Building Respect and Loyalty in Modern Restaurant Organization, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Box: 37, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Leadership With Supervision For Restaurant Efficiency, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Box: 37, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Need For Constant Follow-Up In Successful Restaurant Supervision, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Box: 37, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: A Restaurant Managers Rediscovers The Importance of People, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Box: 37, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Improving Restaurant Operation With The Circulation of Ideas, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Box: 37, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Cashing In With Employee Know-How To Improve Restaurant Efficiency, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Box: 37, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Developing Group and Individual Team Spirit In Your Restaurant, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Box: 37, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Personnel- The Key To Success In Every Phase of Restaurant Operation, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Box: 37, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: How To Get Restaurant Employees To Work With, Not Against You, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Box: 37, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A Restaurant Manager Rediscovers The Importance of People, 1955; Publication (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Box: 37, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Training, 1956; Publication (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Box: 37, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: A Plea For Reason, 1967; Publication (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Box: 37, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Clean Air and Plentiful Fuel, 1969; Publication (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Box: 37, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: A Guide To The Air Quality Act of 1967, Publication (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Box: 37, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Jobsite Safety Program, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Box: 37, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Case Solution Group For Learning Problem Solving, 1955; Publication (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Box: 37, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Training Placement of Unemployment Older Workers, 1963; Publication (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Box: 37, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Operation Negative, 1962; Publication (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Box: 37, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Activities of The National Training Laboratories, 1961; Publication (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Box: 37, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Consultation Program of the National Training Laboratories, 1961; Publication (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Box: 37, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Responsibilities of a Qualified Electrical Contractor, 1954; Publication (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Box: 37, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: National Apprenticeship and Training Standards, Publication (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Box: 37, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Job Rating Plans Used By Nema Member Companies, 1953; Publication (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Box: 37, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Fair Labor Standards Act Regulation On Profit-Sharing and Welfare Plans Revised, 1953; Publication (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Box: 37, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Cooperatives, 1966; Publication (Box 37, Folder 35)
- Box: 37, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: History, 1966; Publication (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Box: 37, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Education In Action, 1966; Publication (Box 37, Folder 37)
- Box: 37, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Youth Activities, 1966; Publication (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Box: 37, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: The Voice of The Family Farmer, 1966; Publication (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Box: 37, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Overtime, 1968; Publication (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Box: 37, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Film Manual, 1958; Publication (Box 37, Folder 41)
- Box: 37, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: A System of Employee Training For Restaurants, 1954; Publication (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Box: 37, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Training, Publication (Box 37, Folder 43)
- Box: 37, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Summary of Apprenticeship Practices In Foundries, Publication (Box 37, Folder 44)
- Box: 37, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1958; Publication (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Box: 37, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Pass Book To Industrial Safety, 1951; Publication (Box 37, Folder 46)
- Box: 37, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Job Classifications & Labor Grades, 1951; Publication (Box 37, Folder 47)
- Box: 37, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Life Insurance, Publication (Box 37, Folder 48)
- Box: 37, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Retirement Planning and Benefits, Publication (Box 37, Folder 49)
- Box: 37, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: NCR World Headquarters, 1978; Publication (Box 37, Folder 50)
- Box: 37, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Application For Employment, 1977; Publication (Box 37, Folder 51)
- Box: 37, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: 1981 National Officers, Publication (Box 37, Folder 52)
- Box: 37, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: The NMA News, 1981; Publication (Box 37, Folder 53)
- Box: 37, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Civil Service Reform, 1980; Publication (Box 37, Folder 54)
- Box: 37, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Exempt Employee Benefits Summary, Publication (Box 37, Folder 55)
- Box: 37, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Employee Rating, 1977; Publication (Box 37, Folder 56)
- Box: 37, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Employee Safety and Security Checklist, 1977; Publication (Box 37, Folder 57)
- Box: 37, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Employee Orientation Checklist, 1977; Publication (Box 37, Folder 58)
- Box: 37, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Data Skills Profile: Affirmative Action Program, 1976; Publication (Box 37, Folder 59)
- Box: 37, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Equal Opportunity Employment At NCR, Publication (Box 37, Folder 60)
- Box: 37, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Office and Technical Benefits Summary, Publication (Box 37, Folder 61)
- Box: 37, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan, 1977; Publication (Box 37, Folder 62)
- Box: 37, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan, 1977; Publication (Box 37, Folder 63)
- Box: 37, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Benefit Provisions, 1977; Publication (Box 37, Folder 64)
- Box: 37, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 37, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: The NCR Employees Credit Union Scholarship, 1970; Publication (Box 37, Folder 65)
- Box: 37, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: For Your Enjoyment, 1960; Publication (Box 37, Folder 66)
- Box: 37, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Old River- Recreation Park, Publication (Box 37, Folder 67)
- Box: 37, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 37, Folder 68)